<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.knime.features.ext.tableau.hyper.bin"
      label="KNIME Tableau Extract API 2.0 (Hyper) Platform specific packages"
      version="3.7.2.qualifier"
      provider-name="KNIME AG, Zurich, Switzerland"
      arch="x86_64">

   <description>
      Tableau Extract API 2.0 (Hyper) binaries for Linux, Mac and Windows.
These binaries are required for the KNIME Tableau (Hyper) nodes.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright by KNIME AG, Zurich, Switzerland
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Terms for License of Tableau Library Feature

0. General
===========
This feature and the Tableau library in binary object code form (&quot;Library&quot;) is provided to you by KNIME AG, Switzerland (&quot;KNIME&quot;) on a special license, that allows you to freely use this feature, but no further rights are granted with this license agreement. You must not extract this feature and/or the Library from its bundle. You may only use it in combination with other features of the KNIME Analytics Platform.
The Library is the intellectual property of Tableau Software, Inc., Seattle, WA, USA (&quot;Tableau&quot;) or its licensors. The Library is protected by law, including without limitation copyright laws, U.S. Patents and Trademarks as noted at http://www.tableausoftware.com/IP. Except for the rights explicitly granted to you in this License Agreement, all right, title and interest in the Library are reserved. You do not acquire any intellectual property or other rights in the Library as a result of downloading the feature or the Library.

1. Use of the Library; Distribution
=====================================
KNIME hereby grants you a personal, limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicenseable license to install and use the feature including the Library. Some components of the Library may be governed by applicable open source software licenses. Your license rights with respect to these individual components are defined by the applicable open source software licenses, and nothing in this license agreement will restrict, limit, or otherwise affect any rights or obligations you may have, or conditions to which you may be subject, under such open source software licenses.

2. Limitations
===============
You may not use the Library for any illegal purpose. You may not, and you will not encourage, assist or authorize any other person to, (a) sell, rent, lease, lend, loan, distribute, act as a service bureau, publicly communicate, transform, or sub-license the Library or otherwise assign any rights to the Library in whole or in part; (b) modify, alter, tamper with, repair, or otherwise create derivative works of the Library, (c) reverse engineer, disassemble, or decompile the Library or apply any other process or procedure to derive the source code of any software included in the Library, (d) extract the feature or the Library from its bundle and use it separately in any way (e) publish the Library for others to copy, (f) use the Library for commercial software hosting services, or (g) access or use the Library in a way intended to avoid incurring fees or exceeding usage limits or quotas.

3. Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability
========================================================
a. YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT INSTALLATION AND USE OF, AND ANY OTHER ACCESS TO, THE LIBRARY IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE LIBRARY IS DELIVERED TO YOU &quot;AS IS&quot; WITH ALL FAULTS AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, AND KNIME DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, ACCURACY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY KNIME OR AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF KNIME WILL CREATE A WARRANTY.

b. TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, KNIME WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR BREACH OF ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY, BREACH OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY RELATED TO THE LIBRARY, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA, OR USE OF THE LIBRARY, EVEN IF KNIME HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN ANY CASE, KNIME&apos;S AGGREGATE LIABILITY UNDER THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT WILL BE LIMITED TO $25.00.

4. Miscellaneous
=================
With this license agreement you receive a license for the Library from KNIME. Tableau and others are the owner of the Library, but KNIME and Tableau are not in any way through this agreement in any kind of partnership, joint venture, or any other relationship - and nothing in this agreement implies this. KNIME is no representative or agent of Tableau and has no authority to enter into any agreement on Tableau&apos;s behalf or on Tableau&apos;s name or otherwise bind Tableau to any agreement or obligation.

5. Source Code
===============
Please see the Tableau technical documentation located on the Tableau website (http://www.tableausoftware.com/) for information on how to retrieve a copy of the source code for certain software components included with the Library, if any.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="org.knime.ext.tableau.hyper.bin.linux.x86_64"
         os="linux"
         arch="x86_64"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.knime.ext.tableau.hyper.bin.macosx.x86_64"
         os="macosx"
         arch="x86_64"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.knime.ext.tableau.hyper.bin.win32.x86_64"
         os="win32"
         arch="x86_64"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.knime.ext.tableau.hyper"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.knime.ext.tableau"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
